Akash Mourya

52 Outram Lane Gtb Nagar Metro, New Delhi, Delhi, 110009, IN • 0919644123189 • akashmourya1919@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

8 years of experience in coordination ang and volunteering, I have achieved tangible results in education, youth development, and community empowerment In 2 years with Shiksha Rath Organization Delhi. I have increased awareness and access to quality education in the region by 45% In 2 years with Muskaan Dream Creative Foundation Gwalior. I created over 20 youth-led Initiatives to promote leadership and life skills. In 4 years as a volunteer at Shri Gaeshdas Ji Maharaj Smriti Shiksha, I increased literacy in the region by 30%

SKILLS -

. Volunteer evaluations

. Schedule coordination

.Volunteer training . Microsoft office

. Department management . Event coordination . Program management

.ChatGpt/Al Tool

EDUCATION

Child development, teaching methodologies, and curriculum development - Bachelor of Education - 2023

Jiwaji University - Gwalior, MP

Sociology - Master of Arts - 2021

Jiwaji University - Gwalior, MP

Mechanical Engineering - Bachelor of Engineering - 2017

Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya - Bhopal, MP

WORK HISTORY

Coordinator - July, 2022 to Present

Shiksha Rath Organization - NEW DELHI, Delhi

- · Coordinated ongoing volunteer publicity and awareness programs.
- · Led new volunteer orientation to organization and programs.
- · Oriented new volunteers on policies and procedures, introduced staff and provided information guides.
- · Communicated regularly with volunteers, assisting with issues and questions.

Coordinator - August, 2017 to December, 2019

Muskaan Foundation - Gwalior, Madhya Pradesh

- · I worked as a coordinator muskaan Foundation to create a world record for the largest education kits distribution.
- . Organized clit meeting to provide project updates
- . Education local community residents about available health and wellness resources

Volunteer Coordinator - June, 2013 to December, 2017

Shri Gaeshdas Ji Maharaj Samiti - Gwalior, MP

- · Maintained up-to-date volunteer calendar coordinating scheduling and staff availability.
- · Developed work schedules according to budgets and workloads, covering priority tasks.
- · Reviewed reports on employee attendance, productivity and effectiveness to evaluate performance.
- · Issued work schedules, duty assignments and deadlines for office or administrative staff.